<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Henrique Dias</title>
    <link>https://henriquedias.com/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Henrique Dias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_GB</language>
    <managingEditor>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://henriquedias.com/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Resolutions for 2016</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/new-year-resolutions-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/new-year-resolutions-2016/</guid>
      <description>One year more has passed. It seems like yesterday I was turning thirteen. Nostalgia. 2015 has been very turbulent and troubled year, but still amazing and meaningful. It has been very antithetical in so many ways I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you. But being that way helped me to grow more than in the years before - growing is a continuous process we should never fear.
 &amp;ldquo;Was it worth doing? Everything’s worth doing / If the soul of the doer isn’t small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portugal is a beautiful country (again)</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/portugal-amazing-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/portugal-amazing-country/</guid>
      <description>Last year, I published a post about how amazing Portugal is. And now I&amp;rsquo;m posting about it again! I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to &amp;ldquo;sell&amp;rdquo; Portugal, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to show how beautiful it is, because it&amp;rsquo;s true!
As I did in the past summer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been visiting some places in my country. I visited Park and National Palace of Pena in Sintra, Vila Viçosa Palace, Redondo and Campo Maior in the last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something about the future. Is it real? Does it exist?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/something-about-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/something-about-future/</guid>
      <description>A word can be a very powerful thing. A word can change lifes, a word can destroy worlds, a word can lead us to other words, a word can make us stop breathing, a word can make us lively, a word can kill us. As you can see, each word is a very special thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m not here to talk about words, am I? No, I&amp;rsquo;m not, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to start with a word: time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop complaining. Do!</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/stop-complaining-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/stop-complaining-do/</guid>
      <description>Everyday I hear people complaining here and there. They complain about almost everything: from the pencil which isn&amp;rsquo;t on its place to the government&amp;rsquo;s rules. I think is doesn&amp;rsquo;t occurs only here, of course. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a problem of adults (some of them, no offense). I see them complaining every single second. If you&amp;rsquo;re not this type of person, I believe you should have seen some of them.
Complaining does:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperfections make us perfect</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/imperfections-make-us-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/imperfections-make-us-perfect/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I look through a window. My bedroom window. It faces the road. I see cars. There are thousand of them. All different: in shape, in colour, in size. But that&amp;rsquo;s only the outside. Their inside is all made of the same essence.
Racism We are all different. That can lead us to a very big problem: racism. &amp;ldquo;He has a different colour, let&amp;rsquo;s take him down!&amp;rdquo; - no! That shouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen, neither here, nor there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 things I would like to be</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/3-things-i-would-like-to-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/3-things-i-would-like-to-be/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following me through the past time, you probably know I want to go further in technology field (if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, read my about page). But it is not the unique thing I would like to be because there are 3 things I would like to be.
When we choose to be something or to follow some field of study, we should think a lot about it to find out if we are sure we want to follow it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the technology a good or a bad thing?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 12:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk a little bit about technology and if it is a good or a bad thing. This article is, of course, according to my point of view. The main question, for now, is &amp;ldquo;is the technology a good or a bad thing?&amp;rdquo;.
What is technology? Firstly, what is technology? I think it is a difficult word to define but according to the dictionary, technology is the science whose objective is the application of technical and scientific knowledge for industrial and commercial purposes so technology isn’t only the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Rei Que Tudo Perdeu</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/o-rei-que-tudo-perdeu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/o-rei-que-tudo-perdeu/</guid>
      <description>Por vezes, a vontade de escrever é tanta que até a tinta desliza pelo papel sem qualquer esforço. Letra a letra. Partícula a partícula. Tudo se compõe.
Trago-vos um pequeno poema (se se pode chamar isso!) que compus em 2012 e que se chama, como podem deduzir, O Rei Que Tudo Perdeu.
 Eu antes tinha terras,
poder e um reino,
para lá governar.
Mas agora sou só
com o meu Bobo a sonhar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have moved, again</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/i-have-moved-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/i-have-moved-again/</guid>
      <description>I have moved, again. From now until the end of the times, coxpe.com and henriquedias.com/blog are gone, and henriquedias.com is the unified version of both.
 &amp;ldquo;Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.&amp;rdquo; - Antoine de Saint-Exupéry
 The quote above tells the main reason I have made this change. The content created by me was dispersed on the web so I moved it all to one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portugal is a beautiful country</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/portugal-beautiful-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/portugal-beautiful-country/</guid>
      <description>Searching, exploring, walking, running, seeing, knowing, watching, meeting, taking photos, etc. All are verbs related with travelling which is one of the most amazing and important things in life.
In the last summer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been visiting various places in my country, Portugal. One of them was Évora that is a city in Alentejo. This is an historical city and it&amp;rsquo;s also beautiful.
After seeing this amazing city, I have searched about this city and I discover that Évora has some places that are considered World Heritage since 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Society and the Objects</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/the-society-and-the-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 20:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/the-society-and-the-objects/</guid>
      <description>Presently, the people love the objects. Sometimes, more than they love the people. Is this good? Or not?
Nowadays, the people buy objects and in the majority of times, they don’t use it. The people just buy objects just to have and not to use.
Another great problem are gifts. If I receive a gift and I don’t like it, should I stay with it or not? In my opinion, I think that offer or donate it is the correct option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SASS - Será a futura versão do CSS?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/sass-sera-a-futura-versao-do-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 10:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/sass-sera-a-futura-versao-do-css/</guid>
      <description>Atualmente, uma das grandes vertentes da programação é a web e esta está muito difundida. Os desenvolvedores web, têm que utilizar várias linguagens de vários tipos: programação, marcação e estilo.
A última versão do CSS (Cascading Style Sheet), o CSS3, trouxe muitas melhorias e novidades tornando-se mais poderoso. Mas será suficiente?
Atualmente, existem várias &amp;ldquo;alternativas&amp;rdquo; e pré-processadores de CSS, como LESS e SASS. Este último, tem vindo a crescer e muitos acreditam que poderá ser a futura versão do CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apresentação</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/apresentacao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 14:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/apresentacao/</guid>
      <description>Olá!
Antes de mais, vou fazer-vos uma breve apresentação minha. O meu nome é Henrique Dias, sou português e vivo em Portugal, no Alentejo. Quero ser Engenheiro de Software e o meu grande objetivo é fazer algo útil para o resto da Humanidade.
Penso que todos deveriam aprender a programar porque além de ser algo muito importante nos dias de hoje, é uma boa forma de nos divertirmos e também treinar o nosso cérebro, estimulando a criatividade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>