<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Henrique Dias</title>
    <link>https://henriquedias.com/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Henrique Dias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://henriquedias.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Resolutions for 2016</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/new-year-resolutions-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/new-year-resolutions-2016/</guid>
      <description>One year more has passed. It seems like yesterday I was turning thirteen. Nostalgia. 2015 has been very turbulent and troubled year, but still amazing and meaningful. It has been very antithetical in so many ways I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you. But being that way helped me to grow more than in the years before - growing is a continuous process we should never fear.
 &amp;ldquo;Was it worth doing? Everything’s worth doing / If the soul of the doer isn’t small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 things I would like to be</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/3-things-i-would-like-to-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/3-things-i-would-like-to-be/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following me through the past time, you probably know I want to go further in technology field (if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, read my about page). But it is not the unique thing I would like to be because there are 3 things I would like to be.
When we choose to be something or to follow some field of study, we should think a lot about it to find out if we are sure we want to follow it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the technology a good or a bad thing?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 12:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk a little bit about technology and if it is a good or a bad thing. This article is, of course, according to my point of view. The main question, for now, is &amp;ldquo;is the technology a good or a bad thing?&amp;rdquo;.
What is technology? Firstly, what is technology? I think it is a difficult word to define but according to the dictionary, technology is the science whose objective is the application of technical and scientific knowledge for industrial and commercial purposes so technology isn’t only the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have moved, again</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/i-have-moved-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/i-have-moved-again/</guid>
      <description>I have moved, again. From now until the end of the times, coxpe.com and henriquedias.com/blog are gone, and henriquedias.com is the unified version of both.
 &amp;ldquo;Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.&amp;rdquo; - Antoine de Saint-Exupéry
 The quote above tells the main reason I have made this change. The content created by me was dispersed on the web so I moved it all to one place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>