<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinion on Henrique Dias</title>
    <link>https://henriquedias.com/tags/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opinion on Henrique Dias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_GB</language>
    <managingEditor>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 08:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://henriquedias.com/tags/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Something about the future. Is it real? Does it exist?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/something-about-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/something-about-future/</guid>
      <description>A word can be a very powerful thing. A word can change lifes, a word can destroy worlds, a word can lead us to other words, a word can make us stop breathing, a word can make us lively, a word can kill us. As you can see, each word is a very special thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m not here to talk about words, am I? No, I&amp;rsquo;m not, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to start with a word: time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop complaining. Do!</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/stop-complaining-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/stop-complaining-do/</guid>
      <description>Everyday I hear people complaining here and there. They complain about almost everything: from the pencil which isn&amp;rsquo;t on its place to the government&amp;rsquo;s rules. I think is doesn&amp;rsquo;t occurs only here, of course. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a problem of adults (some of them, no offense). I see them complaining every single second. If you&amp;rsquo;re not this type of person, I believe you should have seen some of them.
Complaining does:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperfections make us perfect</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/imperfections-make-us-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/imperfections-make-us-perfect/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I look through a window. My bedroom window. It faces the road. I see cars. There are thousand of them. All different: in shape, in colour, in size. But that&amp;rsquo;s only the outside. Their inside is all made of the same essence.
Racism We are all different. That can lead us to a very big problem: racism. &amp;ldquo;He has a different colour, let&amp;rsquo;s take him down!&amp;rdquo; - no! That shouldn&amp;rsquo;t happen, neither here, nor there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the technology a good or a bad thing?</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 12:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/technology-good-bad/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk a little bit about technology and if it is a good or a bad thing. This article is, of course, according to my point of view. The main question, for now, is &amp;ldquo;is the technology a good or a bad thing?&amp;rdquo;.
What is technology? Firstly, what is technology? I think it is a difficult word to define but according to the dictionary, technology is the science whose objective is the application of technical and scientific knowledge for industrial and commercial purposes so technology isn’t only the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>