<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Words on Henrique Dias</title>
    <link>https://henriquedias.com/categories/words/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Words on Henrique Dias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_GB</language>
    <managingEditor>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 13:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://henriquedias.com/categories/words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Verdades Incógnitas</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/verdades-incognitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/verdades-incognitas/</guid>
      <description>Estou a dormir. Ponto. Eu sei que estou a dormir. Sim, eu sei que mais tarde vou ter que me levantar. Não. Não és tu que dizes que eu devo ser. Não és tu que mandas nas minhas ações. Tu não és eu. Sim. Sou eu que mando em mim. Sou eu que ordeno e comando as minhas ações. Não tenho a certeza. Talvez… Tudo é incerto. Será que não sou eu quem manda nas minhas ações?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent Threads</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/intermittent-threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/intermittent-threads/</guid>
      <description>I was there. I turn my head to the left and I see a bullet coming in my direction. The clock stops. I stop. I see myself doing nothing. I see my whole life running throughout my brain. I realize that I haven&amp;rsquo;t done what I should have done. My whole life was a wire, an intermittent wire which is going to eventually break up. I see my children, I see all of the people I love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain State</title>
      <link>https://henriquedias.com/blog/uncertain-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hacdias@gmail.com (Henrique Dias)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquedias.com/blog/uncertain-state/</guid>
      <description>Death. It&amp;rsquo;s the most heard word in the last days. Crime. And they say it was orders from their God. Who&amp;rsquo;s the God? Just someone telling them to kill, to suffocate the people until they die. Why are You doing this? Why is this God telling them to kill this people? Innocents. They didnt do anything. They were people. Just like you, just like me. They were in the wrong place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>